Hi, now we're going to get ready for the gravy.
We're going to coat our turkey neck with oil.
Both sides, we're going to rub it with salt and pepper.
We're going to turn your stove and your pan on to moderately high heat.
We're going to put it in the pan.
And brown it for about three minutes on one side, the turkey neck, and then we're going to flip it over, turn the heat down to moderate heat, brown the other side for ten minutes, and then we will get ready to put in our stock.
We're cooking the turkey neck for three minutes till slightly brown on one side, then flip it over, cook it for ten minutes on the other side.
And turn the heat down to a moderate heat for ten minutes.
Hi, now it's time to add the remaining six cups of stock.
I'm going to pour it into the turkey neck.
I'm going to bring it to a boil.
After it has come to a boil, I'm going to turn the heat down to a simmer, put a lid on it, and simmer it for two hours.
Skimming it every so often.
This will make stock, four and a half cups of stock for your gravy.